ADOLFO JOSE HERNANDEZ APONTE

PROFILE

Mechatronic Engineer and FrontEnd Developer. Experience working with SCRUM and technologies such as React, TypeScript, JavaScript, and Node.js. Basic knowledge in Android, Kotlin, SQL and RPA. Good command of English. Attitude of maintaining continuous learning.

CONTACT

(+57) 3145429669

LinkedIn:

Adolfo Jose Hernandez Aponte.

GitHub:

AJHernandezA.

EMAIL:

adolfohernandezaponte@hotmail.com

SPECIALTIES

Management of software. Analysis and problem solving. Active programming.

SKILLS

Effective communication.
Effective listening.
Good team worker
Evaluation of priorities.
Good pressure management.

HOBBIES

Programming, Read, Tenis, Workout, help animals.

WORK EXPERIENCE

- Mercado Libre [Full-time]

Software Development Analyst. Development and support of applications in React, Typescript, Handlebars, BackBone. Executing solutions in webviews. Tracking of data.

 $[12/2021 - now] \cdot 1 \text{ year 3 months}$

- Upwork. [per-hour]

Freelance. Made web pages in HTML, CSS and JavaScript. [05/2021 – 11/2021] · 6 months

PROJECTS AND COURSES

- Universidad Nacional Autónoma de México- Development of mobile applications with Android.

[06/2020- 12/2020] · 6 months

- HTML, CSS, and JavaScript for Web Developers.

[04/2021-06/2021] · 2 month

- Software Development Colombia (MinTIC).

[02/2021-08/2021] 6 months

- UIPATH - RPA Developer Fundamentals.

[06/2020 - 01/2021] · 6 months

- UIPATH - RPA Business Analyst Fundamentals.

 $[04/2020 - 01/2021] \cdot 8 \text{ months}$

EDUCATION

Universidad Tecnológica de bolívar – Mechatronic Engineer [07/2017 – 01/2023]

Universidad Tecnológica de bolívar – Project management [07/2020 – 07/2021]

Colegio la Nueva Esperanza – Graduete

[01/2004-12/2016]